Guide to the Niels A. Douwes Dekker papers, [ca. 1900]-1950, 1944-1946 (bulk)
Dekker, Niels A. Douwes papers, [ca. 1900]-1950, 1944-1946 (bulk)
- Series I. Photographs
  - The Moluccas (Maluku)
    - Ambon
      - Dancing: 379, 380, 392, 393 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Fishing: 381-389 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Forts (Nieuw Victoria): 390 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Industry: Furniture: 391 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Manners and customs: 394 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Mosques: 395 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Music: 396 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Nutmeg trade: 397-399 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Banda
      - Forts (Fort Nassau): 401-403 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Manners and customs: 404 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Sailboats: 400 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Buru
      - Manners and customs: 405 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Ceram (Seram)
      - Industry: Oil: 1080 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Nature areas: 437-446 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Halmaheira
      - Agriculture: Cacao: 406-411 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Agriculture: Coconuts: 412 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Agriculture: Rice: 413 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Industry: Lumber: 414, 415 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Nature areas: 416, 417, 8510 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Morotai
      - Airports: 418, 419 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Harbors: 420 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Lumber: 421, 422 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Roads: 423 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - New Guinea
      - Agriculture: Rice: 1044 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Agriculture: Sago: Sago grove: 1075 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Agriculture: Sago: Squeezing: 1047-1049 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Agriculture: Sago: Tapping: 1045, 1046 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Airfields (Biak?): 1081 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Architecture, domestic: Arfak: 1092 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Architecture, domestic: Balim/Jayawijaya: 1086, 1094 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Architecture, domestic: Biak: 1088 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Architecture, domestic: Churches: 1084, 1085 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Architecture, domestic: Lake Sentani: 1089-1091 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Architecture, domestic: Marind (Kaya-Kaya): 1083 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Architecture, domestic: Model village (Mugu): 1082 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Architecture, domestic: Wisselmere lakes: 1087 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Arts: Biak--Karwar Style: 1061 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Arts: Geelvink--Bay style: 1053 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Arts: Humboldt--Bay style: 1055 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Arts: Mappi: 1062, 1063 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Arts: Miscellany: 1050-1052, 1064 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Arts: Sepik style: 1056-1060 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Dancing: Balim/Dani: 1076 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Dancing: Marind (Kaya-Kaya): 1077 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Dancing: Papuans: 1078, 1079 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Manners and customs: Dani: 1118 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Manners and customs: Humboldt Bay (?): 1120 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Manners and customs: Lake Sentani: 1121-1124 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Manners and customs: Lowlands: 1126-1128 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Manners and customs: Mappi: 1119 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Manners and customs: Merauke: 1129 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Manners and customs: Miscellany: 1132-1135 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Manners and customs: Motu - (Port Moresby?): 1130, 1131 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Manners and customs: Wisselmere lakes: 1125 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Nature areas: 1095-1117, 4254 (Box 6, Folder 22-24)
      - Road construction (Jayapura area?): 1065-1074, 1093 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Ternate
      - Agriculture: (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Architecture, domestic: 425-427 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Nature areas: 428-432 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Tidore
      - Architecture, domestic: 433-436 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - The Lesser Sunda Islands (Nusa Tenggara)
    - Bali
      - Agriculture: 1144-1151 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Agriculture: 1152-1159 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Architecture: Temples: 1167-1176 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Architecture: Temples: 1177-1183 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Architecture: Museum in Den Pasar: 1166, 1184, 1185 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Architecture: Miscellany: 5479, 5480 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Arts: Carving: 1206-1213 (Box 8, Folder 3-5)
      - Arts: Painting: 1236-1244 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Arts: Pottery: 1245, 1246 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Arts: Puppets: 1247-1257 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
      - Arts: Silverwork: 1260-1268 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Arts: Textile crafts (Ni Polok): 1269 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Dancing: Arja: 1094, 1095 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Dancing: Baris/Jauk: 1125 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Dancing: Barong Landong: 1097 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Dancing: Calonarang (Ranga): 1121-1123 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Dancing: Janger: 1111-1120 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Dancing: Joged: 1101 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Dancing: Kebyer: 1109, 1110 (I Mario) (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Dancing: Ketjak: 1103-1108 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Dancing: Legong: 1126-1138 (Box 8, Folder 11-12)
      - Dancing: Ngurek: 1124 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Dancing: Ni Polok: 1139, 1140 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Dancing: Sanghyiang Dedari: 1098-1100 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Dancing: Tanan Garudo: 1096 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Dancing: Trunajaya: 1102 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Industry: Refrigeration: 4308 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Livestock: 1142, 1143 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Manners and customs: 1186-1194 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Manners and customs: Boy Scouts: 1204 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Manners and customs: Cockfighting: 1195 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Manners and customs: Fishing: 1196, 1197 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Manners and customs: Market: 1198 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Manners and customs: Miscellany: 8481, 8482 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Manners and customs: Ni Polok: 1199, 1200 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Manners and customs: Sailing: 1205 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Manners and customs: Transmigration: 1201, 1202 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Manners and customs: Tuak vendor: 1203 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Music: Gong ensemble: 1139, 1140 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Music: Miscellany: 1141 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Nature areas: 1160-1165, 4309, 4310 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Rites and ceremonies (excluding death ritual): Offerings (Odalan): 1270, 1272 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Rites and ceremonies (excluding death ritual): Offerings (Odalan): Ni Polok: 1271 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Rites and ceremonies (excluding death ritual): Prayers: 1273 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Rites and ceremonies (excluding death ritual): Priests (Metabuh): 1274 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Rites and ceremonies (excluding death ritual): Weddings: 1275 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Rites and ceremonies (excluding death ritual): Weddings: Giangyar (Anak Agung Gde Oka and Tjokorde Istri Sri Mas, August 14, 1948): 1276-1282 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Flores
      - Agriculture: Copra: 1283-1287 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Agriculture: Corn: 4322 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Agriculture: Rice: 1288-1299 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Architecture, domestic: 1301-1303, 4327, 4328 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Dancing: 1304-1307 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Flora and fauna: 4323-4326 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Livestock: 1355 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Manners and customs: 1325-1332, 4329, 4330 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Cockfighting: 1333-1341 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Music: 1300 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Nature areas: 1316 (in Manners and customs file: Cockfighting): 1317-1324, 4311-4315 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Rites and ceremonies: "Spiderweb Garden" ritual: 1342-1352, 1354 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Rites and ceremonies: Catholicism: 1353 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Textile crafts: Ginning: 1308 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Textile crafts: Spinning: 1309, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Textile crafts: Weaving: 1310-1315 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Komodo
      - Flora and fauna: 4333, 4334 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Flora and fauna: Komodo dragon: 8511 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Lomblen
      - Architecture, domestic: 341, 1356, 1357 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Churches: 342-346 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Fishing: 347-365 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Manners and customs: 366-371, 4335 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Textile crafts: 372, 373 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Lombok
      - Manners and customs: 317, 318 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Rites and ceremonies: Pare-Sean (Selong): 319 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Roti
      - Manners and customs: 299-303 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Sumba
      - Architecture, domestic: Prailin (East Sumba): 14 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Livestock: 289-291 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Rites and ceremonies: Purungu ta Kadonga Ratu (West Sumba): 292-294 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Textile crafts: Ginning cotton: 295, 296 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Textile crafts: Spinning: 297, 298 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Sumbawa
      - Livestock: Horseracing: 305-309 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Livestock: Manners and customs: 310, 311 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Rites and ceremonies: Sultan of Sumbawa's 15 Year Jubilee (1947): 312-315 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Rites and ceremonies: Timorese Raja visiting the Jubilee: 316, 336 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Timor
      - Agriculture: 304, 329 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Dancing/martial arts: Sword dance: 320-322 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Dancing/martial arts: Likorai: 323 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Decoration and ornament: 324-328, 337 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Manners and customs: 330-335 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Manners and customs: Nature scenes: 338 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Manners and customs: Schools: 339 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Music: 304, 4414, 4415 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Java
    - Agriculture
      - Cabbage: 1631 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Cacao: 1632 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Cassava: 1633, 1634 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Cinchona bark: 1635 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Forestry schools: 1636-1659 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Nutmeg: 1660-1662 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Rice: 1744-1809 (Box 9, Folder 2-6)
      - Rice: 1810-1834 (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
      - Rubber: 1663-1667 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Sisal: 1668 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Soybeans: 1669 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Sugar: 1670-1672, 1835 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Tea: 1673-1687 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
      - Tea: 1688-1699 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Teak: 1700-1703 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Vegetable cultivation (miscellany): 1704 (Box 9, Folder 9-11)
      - Experimental Agricultural Station in Cipanas: 1708-1743 (Box 9, Folder 9-11)
    - Architecture
      - Almshouse: 1836 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Bamboo: 4420, 4421 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Bantam: 1837-1842, 1843-1852, 1853-1859 (Box 9, Folder 12-14)
      - Kraton (Jogja/Solo): 1860-1864 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Miscellany: 1865-2002 (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
      - Miscellany: 2003-2012 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Miscellany: 2013-2051 (Box 9, Folder 17-20)
    - Arts
      - Carving: 2052-2055 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Chinese painting: 2215 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Coconut palm: 2088 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Film-making: 2056-2065, 2068-2071, 2073-2075, 2078 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Photography: 2079 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Puppetry (Chinese): 2092 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Silverwork: 2080-2087, 2091 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Wayang: Golek: 2205-2214 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Wayang: Kulit: 2093-2099 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Wayang: Kulit: 2200-2204 (Sumatra) (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Weaving: 2090 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Batavia, pre-1900
      - Batavia, pre-1900: 2145-2313 (Box 11, Folder 5-8)
    - Bridges
      - Bridges: 505, 2314-2325, 3060 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Dancing/martial arts
      - Bondan: 2093 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Golek: 2094-2096 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Kuda Kepang/Lumping: 2098, 2099 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Payung: 2100 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Penjoentro: 2144 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Sandiwara (drama): 2103-2113, 2123 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Silat: 2101-2102 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Srimpi/Bedaya: 2114-2122 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Tayuban: 2124-2126 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Topeng Panji: 2127-2131 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Wayang Wong: 2132-2143 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Flora and fauna
      - Flora and fauna: 263, 3061-3068 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Buitenzorg (Bogor): 762, 3069-3087, 3089, 3090 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Museum specimens: 3091-4000 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Harbors
      - Harbors: 2326-2379 (Box 11, Folder 14-17)
      - Harbors: 2380-2457 (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
      - Harbors: 2458-2464, 4152, 4153 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Healthcare
      - Dentist's chair: 2469 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Doctor's arrival at Tanjung Priok: 2470, 2471 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Eykman Institute: 2472-2480 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Geneeskundig Hogeschool: 2469 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Hygienisch-reportage: 2482, 2483 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Mantri examination: 2484 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Med. Faculteit te Batavia: 2485, 2486 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Med. Faculteit v/d U.I.: 2487-2489, 2510, 2511 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Miscellany: 2490-2493 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - N.I.R.O. Laboratory: 2494-2502 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Pasteur Institute: 2503-2505, 2509 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Rumah Sakit Poesat: 2506 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - St. Caroles Hospital: 2507 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Zendings Kraamkliniek: 2508 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Industry
      - Automobiles: 4017, 4018 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Breweries: 4021-4025 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Canning: 4026, 4027 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Cigarettes: 4031-4041 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Clay: 4100, 4102-4105 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Construction (buildings): 4042, 4043 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Copper: 4044 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Dolls: 4047 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Electric (Philips): 4048-4055 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Fishing (ice for storage): 4057, 4060, 4061 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Furniture: 4058, 4059 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Glass, bottling: 4062-4071 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Hats: 4072, 4073 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Kapok: 4074, 4075 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Machinery factories: de Arbeid (Semarang): 4045, 4046, 4115 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Machinery factories: Braat (Surabaya): 4116-4121 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Machinery factories: Miscellany (Blora): 4122 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Madiun series: 4134-4151 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Mills: 4057, 4060, 4061 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Mines and mineral resources: 4129-4133 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Pottery: 4076 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Printing: 4077-4085 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Rubber: 4086-4089, 4123 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Salt (Madura): 4090-4095 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Sandals: 4096 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Sisal: 4097, 4098 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Sugar: 4099 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Telephones: 4106-4112 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Textiles: Batik cap: 4255-4262, 4286, 4287 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Textiles: Batik tulis: 4263-4270 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Textiles: Handloom weaving: 4273-4280 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Textiles: Handloom weaving: Madura: 4281 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Textiles: Hand spinning: 4282 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Textiles: Hand spinning: Madura: 4283, 4284 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Textiles: Machine weaving: 4285, 4288-4292 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Textiles: Rug-making (Peking Carpetworks): 4271, 4272 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Umbrellas: 4113, 4114 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Islam
      - Bandung: 4423-4427 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Bantam: 4428-4438 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Jakarta: 4439-4449 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Madura: 4450-4453 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Miscellany: 4454-4479 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Muslim affairs, 1942-1947: 5359-5373 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Pilgrimage: 4480-4483 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Semarang: 4484 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Series on Muslim affairs, 1942-1947: 5359-5373 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Solo: 4485 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Livestock/poultry
      - Bulls: 2525 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Cows: 2513-2545 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Cows: Madurese cows: 2526 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Ducks: 2512 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Oxen: 2537-2539 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Ram fights (Badung): 2527 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Steer fights (Djember): 2528, 2529 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Water buffaloes: 2530-2536, 2540-2544 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Manners and customs
      - Banks: 5039, 5040 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Birds as pets: 4486, 4487 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Children's amusements: 4488-4495 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Cinemas: 4496-5000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Collecting Kini Fruit: 5001 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Family life: 5002-5022 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
      - Fashion show in Hotel des Indes: 5023 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Fishing: 5024-5028 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Gambling: 5029-5031 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Gambling: Cockfighting: 5032-5038 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Miscellany: 5039-5049 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Orangutans as pets: 5050 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Orphanages: 5051-5055 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Report on Ny. Raden Ayu Malia Soenario: 5056-5058 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Schools: 5059-5073 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Vendors: 5074-5115 (Box 13, Folder 11-13)
      - Women washing clothes: 5116-5121 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Markets/shops
      - Markets/shops: 5122-5151 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
    - Monuments
      - Monuments: 5152-5167 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Music
      - Batak students' performance in Batavia: 4209, 4210 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Church concerts: 4175-4179 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Gamelan: Javanese: 4155-4160 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Gamelan: Sudanese: 4161 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Gamelan: Tjokrowasito (KRT Wasitodipuro): 4162 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Krontjong: 4164-4174 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Madura (music ensemble): 4163 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Musical/dramatic performances for radio: 4187-4195, 4197-4208 (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
      - Queen's Day celebration in Batavia: 4180-4182 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Western instrumental ensembles: 4183-4186 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Nature areas
      - Nature areas: 264, 2632-3019 (Box 15, Folder 5-12)
      - Nature areas: 3020-3039, 4011-4016 (Box 14, Folder 10-11)
      - Nature areas: 4001-4010 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Eruption of Gedeh (plus 1 page of descriptive text): 3040-3056 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Power plants/electric stations
      - Power plants/electric stations: 4416-4419 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Rites and ceremonies
      - Bantam cannon: 4337 (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
      - Bondowoso miracle (1948): 4365-4384 (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
      - Circumcision: 4353-4357 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Feast Day in Salatiga (1948): 4345 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Feast Day in Semarang (1948): 4359-4361 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Festival for Dewi Landjar at Wiradesa (1948): 4338-4340 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Jacatra cannon: 4336 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Kerapan Sapi (Madura): 4385-4405 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Offering place in Pati: 4346-4348 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Queen's Day celebration in Batavia (1949): 4341 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Queen's Day celebration in Semarang: 4349-4352 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Queen's Day celebration in Surabaya (1947): 4358 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Selamatan preparations?: 4342, 4343 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified parade: 4364 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Weddings: 4406-4410 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Weddings: Daughter of Hoesen Djajadinmgrat: 4411-4413 (negative) (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - West Java River Festival: 4344 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Sailboats
      - Sailboats (including Madura): 4211-4229 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Sailboats (including Madura): 4230-4247 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Sailboats (including Madura): 4248-4253 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Temples and churches
      - Churches: 5168-5172 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Contemporary Chinese temples: 5173-5177 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Hindu-Buddhist temples: 5178-5271 (Box 16, Folder 6-11)
      - Hindu-Buddhist temples: 5205-5216 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Transportation
      - Transportation: 5272-5356 (Box 16, Folder 12-17)
      - Transportation: 5326-5329, 5374 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Trishaw drivers: 5357-5358 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Death ritual
    - Bali: 1358-1392 (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
    - Bantam: 1596-1610 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Batak: 1611-1613 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Batavia: Funeral of Dr. R. Tumbelaka: 1620 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Borneo (Ngaju): 1394-1399, 1401-1420, 1422-1432 (Box 17, Folder 7-10)
    - Borneo (Ngaju): 1400, 143-1440, 239, 1900 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Celebes (Minahassa): 1618 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Celebes (Toraja): 1476-1521 (Box 17, Folder 11-14)
    - Celebes (Toraja): 1522-1545, 1556-1559, 1561-1568, 1570-1586, 4321 (Box 18, Folder 1-6)
    - Celebes (Toraja): 1587-1595 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Chinese: 1441-1470, 4422 (Box 18, Folder 7-9)
    - Chinese: Dr. Kwa Tjoan Sioe: 1471 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Chinese: Ghost marriage: 1472-1474 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Chinese: Chinese grave in Merauke: 1475 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Kudus: 1621 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Madura: 1619 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Medan: 1625 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Miscellany: 1623, 1624 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - New Guinea: 1614, 1615 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Rembang (Kartini's grave): 1622 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Samosir: 1617 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Revolution
    - Armed forces
      - 5374-5397 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - 5374-5397 (negatives) (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - 5398-5427 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - 5428-5447 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - 5448-5477 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - 5478-5507 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - 5508-5537 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - 5538-5557 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - 5558-5568 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - 5398-5440, unnumbered (negatives), guerrilla drills in Jogja, 1946 (negatives) (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Atrocities/arrests/executions
      - 5569-5588 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - 5589-5608 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - 5609-5628 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - 5629-5649 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - 5569-5608 (negatives) (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - 5609-5649 (negatives) (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - 5650-5667 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - 5668-5685, unnumbered negatives (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - 5686-5697 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - 8510-8552 (photograph "album" of Chinese atrocities) (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Conferences/meetings
      - 5698-5712 (prints and negatives) (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - 5713-5752 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - 5753-5792 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - 5793-5832 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - 5833-5872 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - 5873-5912 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - 5913-5952 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - 5953-5992 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - 5993-6032 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - 6033-6072 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - 6073-6112 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - 6113-6152 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - 6153-6191 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - 6192-6231 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - 6232-6271 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - 6272-6311 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - 6312-6351 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - 6352-6391 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - 6392-6431 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - 6432-6471 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - 6472-6516 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - 6517-6746 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - 6747-6776 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - 6777-6796, unnumbered negatives (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - 6797-6816 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - 6817-6832 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - 6833-6844 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - 6845-6855 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - 6856-6888 (election for Banyuwangi Report) (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Daily life/evacuees/internees
      - 6889-6928 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - 6929-6968 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - 6969-7008 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - 7009-7048 (Box 22, Folder 10)